sleeplikethedead.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement for Sleep Like The Dead

Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of extreme importance to Sleep Like The Dead.  Our reputation and integrity are directly related to the trust we have with our visitors. Below is a description of how Sleep Like The Dead strives to protect the privacy of Internet users.

Users  
All users who simply visit the Sleep Like The Dead website retain total personal anonymity. We do not acquire or collect any personal information about you when you visit. And we do not require you to give us personal information to browse our website. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private properties. Sleep Like The Dead does, however, collect non-identifiable personal information which is specific to how you use our website. 

Our  servers record non-personally identifying details such as, but not limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, your IP address, the date and time, the duration of your visit and the pages viewed. This information is obtained only for the purpose of determining the number of visits each of our pages receive, how much time our visitors spend viewing our articles and home many pages each of our visitors view.  This information is pooled for statistical purposes.

There are instances when a user may provide specific personal information when filling out a form on our site.  This information is kept in absolute confidence and is not shared with any other organization. 

Furthermore, we do not collect or sell the email addresses or demographic information of "casual visitors," which are people who visit pages on our website but do not fill out forms.

Cookies  
Sleep Like The Dead uses cookies for collecting such general information as how many people visit our site, how long they stay, and how many pages they view.  No personal information is obtained with cookies.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire.

However, if you block cookies from our website by changing the settings of your browser or by using an Internet security firewall program, you may not have access to portions of our content.  These security programs can block important graphics and other content which are not harmful to you. 

We are a legitimate informational website with no interest in misdirecting you, "hijacking" your web browser or using the disreputable tactics that some other web sites may employ. 

Advertising Seen on Sleeplikethedead.com  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Sleeplikethedead.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors to our site based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Sleep Like The Dead may use outside organizations to provide advertising for our site. The links on these ads may contain cookies that the advertiser uses to track the ad's effectiveness. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by the advertiser(s), and we do not have access or control over this information. 

Though we try to maintain relationships with only the most reputable advertisers, we have no control over their policies or procedures and cannot accept responsibility for their actions.  However, we welcome any questions and/or complaints regarding any ads posted on our website.

External Links  
This site contains links to other websites or references to off line information sources. Sleep Like The Dead is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites or sources.  

Security  
Sleep Like The Dead has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.  Email messages sent to us do not reside on a networked server and are inaccessible except for authorized persons in our employ. 

Disclosure regarding changes in this policy  
Sleep Like The Dead has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please contact us.

We reserve the right to change, clarify or extend this policy statement from time to time based on our needs, the needs of our visitors, changes in technology or changes in applicable law. 

However, at no time will information which you provided to us in confidence be intentionally released to any organization or person without your permission.

We will not retroactively change our privacy policy for the purpose of intentionally releasing your personal information without your permission.
